[
    {
        "questionNo": "Q1.",
        "question": "Predicates can only include a finite verb.",
        "options": [
            "Correct",
            "Incorrect"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q2.",
        "question": "Subjects can be noun equivalents.",
        "options": [
            "Correct",
            "Incorrect"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q3.",
        "question": "My family loves mountainous holiday destinations. In the above sentence the simple subject is:",
        "options": [
            "My",
            "My Family",
            "Family",
            "Destinations"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q4.",
        "question": "Pat Cummins, in the Australian Cricket team remains the -ranked bowler in Test cricket. In the above sentence the simple subject is:",
        "options": [
            "Pat",
            "Pat Cummins",
            "Australian Cricket team",
            "In the Australian Cricket team"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q5.",
        "question": "Only Coordinating conjunctions can help in the formation of Compound subjects.",
        "options": [
            "Correct",
            "Incorrect"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q6.",
        "question": "A pre-modifier includes:",
        "options": [
            "Regular Adjectives",
            "Determiners",
            "Articles",
            "Both A and B"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q7.",
        "question": "Complements are a part of:",
        "options": [
            "Compound predicate",
            "Predicates",
            "Complete Predicate",
            "Both A and B"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q8.",
        "question": "They are playing near the out-house. In the above sentence the verb phrase is:",
        "options": [
            "Are",
            "Playing",
            "Are playing",
            "Are playing near the out-house"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q9.",
        "question": "They came here but left early. The predicate in the sentence is:",
        "options": [
            "Came here",
            "Left early",
            "Both A and B",
            "Came here but left early"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q10.",
        "question": "I did not sleep well last night. The complete predicate in the above sentence includes:",
        "options": [
            "The verb phrase ‘did not sleep’",
            "A phrase which answers the ‘when?’",
            "The object ‘well’",
            "Both A and B"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q11.",
        "question": "What will you term the components of the list below togetherly? Articles(A, An, The), Possessive, Adjectives(my, your, her, his…), Demonstrative Adjectives(this, that…), Quantifiers(Any, Some, Many, All…) and Numbers",
        "options": [
            "Modifiers",
            "Mitigators and Intensifiers",
            "Determiners",
            "Both A and B"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q12.",
        "question": "Simple predicates exclude:",
        "options": [
            "Modifiers",
            "Objects",
            "Complements",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q13.",
        "question": "Mars rotates on its axis once every 24.6 hours. In the sentence above select the object from the complete predicate.",
        "options": [
            "Axis",
            "On its axis",
            "Every 24.6 hours",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q14.",
        "question": "I went home. This sentence contains:",
        "options": [
            "A simple subject",
            "A complete predicate",
            "No complete subject",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q15.",
        "question": "Sit down. The subject in this sentence is:",
        "options": [
            "You",
            "Not mentioned but understood",
            "Passive",
            "Both A and B"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q16.",
        "question": "A prepositional phrase can be a part of:",
        "options": [
            "Equivalents",
            "Post-modifier",
            "Both A and B",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q17.",
        "question": "Jupiter rotates once every 10 hours, Saturn spins once every 11 hours, and Neptune completes a rotation in 16 hours. The above sentence has a:",
        "options": [
            "Simple subject",
            "Compound subject",
            "Complete subject",
            "Both A and C"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q18.",
        "question": "Pre-modifier +......................... +..................is a way of forming complete subjects.",
        "options": [
            "subject , post-modifier",
            "post-modifier , subject",
            "Subject, phrases",
            "Noun equivalents, phrases"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q19.",
        "question": "Pluto is so distant from the centre of our solar system that our Sun would look like a very bright star in its sky! What is the predicate in the above sentence?",
        "options": [
            "Is so distant from the centre of the solar system that",
            "Would look like a very bright star in its sky",
            "Both A and B",
            "There is a single predicate"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q20.",
        "question": "In a sentence, a subject might not be committing any action.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    }
]
